Guide to the Rice University Archives Studies in English Literature 1500-1900 records, 1959-2020 UA 057
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: SEL Articles, Reviews, Manuscripts, 2018-2020
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 58, Issue 3, Summer 2018 (Box 252)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 58, Issue 4, Autumn, 2018 (Box 253)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 59, Issue 1, Winter 2019 (Box 254)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 59, Issue 2, Spring 2019 (Box 255)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 59, Issue 3, Summer 2019 (Box 256)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 59, Issue 4, Autumn 2019 (Box 257)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 60, Issue 1, Winter 2020 (Box 258)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 60, Issue 2, Spring 2020 (Box 259)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 60, Issue 3, Summer 2020 (Box 260)
  - Original pages, Comparisons, Author Envelopes for Vol. 60, Issue 4, Autumn 2020 (Box 261)